Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1940-1949
    - Safanie, Alvin Harold, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      1924-2008
    - Sauter, Robert Anthony, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      1925-2006
    - Schaer, William George, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Schimoler, Louis Charles, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      1923-2006
    - Scholtz, Eugene Rudolf, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      1918-2000
    - Stevens, Alan Douglas, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      1926-2011
    - Taylor, Clark Alexander, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      1908-1964
    - Maurer, Fred Dry, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      1909-2001
    - Anderson, Howard Frederick, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Baker, Lyle Adelbert, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Birchard, Raymond Finney, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 55)
      1926-2006
    - Blaney, Arthur James, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Bonn, George Robert, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      1920-1949
    - Buckley, Donald Faust, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Christensen, George Curtis, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      See also Faculty file; Various photographs
    - Cohen, Bennett Jay, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      1925-1990
    - Cosgrove, Albert Sippel, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Daniels, Willard Herbert, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Davis, F. Langdon, Jr., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Dickinson, Bruce Richard, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Dingley, Dana Coolidge, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Fagan, Mortimer Moses, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Frederick, Christabel Hamilton, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 67)
      Thirty first woman graduate
    - Gale, Robert F., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Glick, Stanley, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 69)
      1937-
    - Goldman, Robert A., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 70)
      Contents incomplete
    - Greene, William Arthur, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Heath, Richard L., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 72)
      1918-1947
      No class photo; various photographs
    - Hsia, Ting-you, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 73)
      From Peoples Republic of China
    - Jensen, Wayne Ivan, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Keaton, William Henry, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 75)
      1924-2015
    - Lunna, Richard Carlton, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - McCormick, John Elliott, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - McEnerney, Philip John, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Miller, Albert Wank, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 79)
      1927-2001
    - Quimby, Herbert Hugh, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Reddick, Harry E., Jr., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Reinhard, Karl Raymond, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Roe, Muriel Osgood, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 83)
      Thirty second woman graduate
    - Schmitt, William Francis, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Sharpe, Malcolm Mark [Shapiro, Moe or Moses], 1949 (Box 11, Folder 85)
      1920-2005
    - Stewart, Marianne Frances Smith, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 86)
      Thirty third woman graduate
    - Taylor, William Edward, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 87)
      1924-1977?
    - Vargoshe, Richard Edwin, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Wang, Hung Chang, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 89)
      1914?-2002
    - Ward, Gerald Merritt, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 90)
    - Webster, Donald Eugene, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 91)
      1921-2014
    - Wheaton, James Robert, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - White, Raymond Hamilton, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 93)
    - Wight, James Beattie, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 94)
    - Williamson, Jane Louise, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 95)
    - Yasgur, Isidor, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 96)
      1926-2010
  - 1950-1959
    - Adsit, Milton Eugene, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 97)
      1925-2000
    - Aldrich, Stanley M., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 98)
    - Beakman, LaVerne M., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 99)
    - Crispell, Donald Heath, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 100)
    - Darrow, William Patrick, Jr., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 101)
      Member of class of 1949, but received DVM in 1950
    - Deutsch, Henry J., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 102)
      1923-2012
    - Fuechsel, Robert Edward, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 103)
      1926-2001
    - Garrison, Stanley Earl, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 104)
      1918-2008
    - Gay, William Ingalls, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Grogan, Joseph William, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Haenel, William Frederick, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 107)
    - Hammond, James Francis, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 108)
    - Hannigan, Daniel John, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 109)
    - Harris, Robert James, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 110)
      1917-2015
    - Hixon, Alvin Eugene, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 111)
      1918-2010
    - Holzworth, Jean, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 112)
      1915-2007
      Thirty fourth woman graduate
    - Jones, Eugene Miles, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - Jones, Stuart Van Scoten, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - Lambert, Ronald Dennis, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - Lawrence, George Edward, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 116)
      1917-1997
    - Lewis, Anson Comstock, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - Loomis, Vader Madison, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 118)
    - Markham, Claron Evans, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 119)
    - McCarthy, Gerald Edward, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - McKenna, Vincent Edward, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Miller, Wilson Leroy, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 122)
      1917-2004
    - Morris, Robert George, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Ostrander, John Philip, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Padget, Paul Warren, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - Palmer, Lynn Gage, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Peckham, Malcolm Curtis, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Phillips, Seeley McCombs, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Puleo, Joseph, Jr., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Raemsch, Robert Paul, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - Rich, John W., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - Rockwell, Stewart Ray, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - Ross, Simeon Leon, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - Schmidt, Milton, Jr., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - Severson, Alfred Oscar, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - Sickles, Walter John, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 136)
      1917-1971
    - Siegrist, Jacob Calvin, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - Simon, Harold Frederick, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Simon, Norman, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - Stack, Robert James, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Szlachta, Henry Leo, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      1928-
    - Tuthill, Dallas Bryden, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Uhlendorf, Albert Henry, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      1924-2005
    - Van Aken, John Lansing, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Wicks, George William, Jr., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Zimmerman, Manuel, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Abel, William, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Allen, Charles Raymond, Jr., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      1925-2001
    - Baker, John Stewart, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Biberstein, Ernst Ludwig, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bither, Henry Dean, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Bo, Howard Allan, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Burr, Isaac Tucker, III, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Cello, Robert Morgan, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      1921-2001
    - Christensen, George Manford, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Davidson, James Carl, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Decher, Robert Everett, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - DeGoosh, Coburn Pushee, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Dobrinsky, John Joseph, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Drumm, Richard Henry, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Easton, Cleon Weldon, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      1925-2011
    - Elliott, Donald Jenison, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      1929-
    - Farrell, Robert David, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      1927-2005
    - Gandal, Charles Paul, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      1928-2012
    - Georgi, Jay Robert, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      1928-2015
    - Hendricks, Marion, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      1923-1978
    - Howlett, Harlan John, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Hughes, David Edward, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Isachsen, Nils Oivind, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Jones, Merlin Herbert, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      1927-2010
    - Kronman, Kenneth, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Kreutter, Walter Paul, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Leventhal, Allan Abraham, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      1923-2002
    - Malnati, Peter Louis, Jr., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Mara, John Lawrence, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Martin, James Francis, Jr., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      1924-1972?
    - Meleny, William Phelps, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Miner, Paul Wesley, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Mueller, Herbert Carl, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Nangeroni, Louis Lindo, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Parsons, Byron Wilson, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Petherbridge, Colin, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Pilger, Charles Elwood, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Roberts, Kent Clayton, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Robinson, John William, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      1925-2005
    - Roy, William Edson, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Schaffer, Myron Holt, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 48)
      1924-2001
    - Sickles, John Stephen, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Smith, Richard Alvin, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 50)
      1928-1998
    - Sullivan, Edward Marshall, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Underwood, Arthur Mead, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Weeks, John Elmer, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Widger, Bruce William, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Baldwin, John Hoag, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Blaisdell, Edwin Ellis, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Brennan, John Joseph, Jr., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 57)
      See also Collection #6579, Brennan, John Joseph, Jr. papers, 1947-1952, n.d.
    - Boerenko, Henry Dudka [or Duka], 1952 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Chamberlain, Kenneth W., Jr., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      1925-2002
    - Clark, Robert Emmett, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      1929-2006
    - Davidson, William Arthur, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      1927-2012
    - DePuy, Peter Justin, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Doty, Michael Earley, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Duberman, Daniel, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Durniak, Daniel, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Flannery, James Joseph, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Ford, Donald Clark, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      1930-
    - Fuess, Robert Warren, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      1929-2008
    - Goergi, Marion E. Schott, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Gorse, George Edward, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      1925-2015
    - Gourley, James Armstrong, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Graff, Rodger Frederick, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 72)
      1926-1952
    - Grano, Edward, Jr., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 73)
      1925-1994
    - Grass, Albert Everett, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Greenstein, Edward Theodore, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 75)
    - Greenwood, Albert Roundy, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 76)
      1920-1957
    - Hagstad, Harry Victor, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    - Haynes, Nelson Bruce, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    - Henry, Donald Edward, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 79)
    - Hoff, Edwin James, Jr., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Keeler, William Emerson, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Kuhn, James Francis, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 82)
      1924-1965
    - Loomis, Wendell King, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Marks, Herbert Richard, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Martin, Robert Stuart, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 85)
      1921-2015
    - McCarthy, John B., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 86)
      1931-2012
    - McVicar, John West, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 87)
    - Milkey, Robert King, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 88)
    - Myers, Charles Leroy, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Paddock, Joseph Emory, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 90)
      1927-2014
    - Paquette, Ernest Frederick, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Pelham, Paul Herman, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 92)
      1929-1996
    - Rackowski, Edward John, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Rooney, James Rowell, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 94)
      1927-2008
    - Shupe, James LeGrande, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Thorington, Gerald LeGrand, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 96)
      1920-2011
    - Tomidy, Kasimier Michael, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Trowbridge, Robert Denny [or Denney], 1952 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - Vreeland, Everett Woodruff, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 99)
      1925-2012
    - Wainwright, Robert Mitchell, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - Wilson, Jean Thomas, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Winnick, Edward Peter, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 102)
    - Boardman, Crager John, Sr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 103)
    - Boroson, Elihu Bertrand, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 104)
      1928-2013
    - Buckley, Patrick Coughlin, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 105)
    - Buell, William Charles, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 106)
    - Chandler, Robert Louis, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 107)
    - Clause, Charles Franklin, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 108)
    - Croshaw, Joseph Ellis, Jr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 109)
    - Crowell, Laurence Ralph, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 110)
    - Dann, LaVerne Sidney, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 111)
    - Davis, Garrie Robert, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 112)
    - Di Bitetto, Daniel Frank, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 113)
    - Draudt, Richard Philip, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Ebersol, Milton Farney, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 115)
    - Goldfinger, Lewis Adolph, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 116)
    - Goodman, Laurence William, Jr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - Greiner, Arthur Edwin, Jr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 118)
    - Hall, Charles Edwin, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - Harter, Richard Warren, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 120)
      1927-1961
    - Hayes, Gerald Loring, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - Hoffman, Paul Eugene, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - Hull, Stanley Hanford, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - Jacobson, Louis Heinz, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 124)
    - Lewis, Frederick Townsend, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 125)
    - Lewis, Jordan, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 126)
      1927-2013
    - Lindblom, Arthur Oscar, Jr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 127)
    - Lunna, Robert Preston, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 128)
    - Mead, Warren William, Jr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 129)
    - Mitchell, William Leo, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 130)
    - Motta, Arthur P., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 131)
    - Nelson, Robert Carl, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 132)
    - Nezvesky, Louis Oliver, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 133)
    - Plumer, Gilbert John, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Rapp, Franklin Willard, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Robbins, Joseph Herman, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 136)
      1924-2011
    - Rowan, Mary Hortense Ford, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 137)
    - Sanderson, Charles Wilson, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 138)
    - Schlomchug [Coleman], Danny Charles, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 139)
      1929-2013
    - Shor, Aaron Louis, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Simpson, Francis Albert, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Stack, William Francis, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Sumner, George Wymon, Jr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Thorne, Joseph LeRoy, Jr., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 144)
    - Twinging, William Jarvis, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 145)
    - Wineyard, George Dare, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 146)
    - Williamson, Russell Lelong, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 147)
    - Winokur, Erwin Bernard, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 148)
      1926-2003
    - Aaronson, Morton, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 149)
    - Berry, Nicholas, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 150)
    - Cameron, Thomas Price, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 151)
    - Carroll, William Edward, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 152)
      1927-1975
    - Coates, Helen Virginia, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 153)
    - Corr, Clyde Alton, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - Deeley, Maurice George, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 155)
    - Delahunt, Charles Samuel, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 156)
      1928-1967
    - Dellers, Robert William, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 157)
    - Dygert, Dewitt David, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 158)
    - Fellenbaum, Stanley, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - Freedman, Robert William, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 160)
    - French, Herbert Root, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 161)
    - Freund, Richard Alan, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 162)
    - Fritz, Donald Harold, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 163)
    - Hume, William Towne, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 164)
    - Hyde, John Landis, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 165)
      1924-2010
    - Kahrs, Robert Frederick, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - Kavanaugh, John F., 1954 (Box 12, Folder 167)
      1928-2000
    - Lebish, Irwin Joel, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Lerner, Murray Martin, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lewis, Bertram, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Marsh, Henri Carroll, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      1930-2001
    - Marshall, Vincent, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Matochik, John Andrew, Jr., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Maurice, George Eugene, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - McBride, Keith Ferris, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Melby, Edward Carlos, Jr., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Messersmith, Robert E., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Miller, Richard Eugene, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Robert Douglas, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      1927-1970
    - Murray, Garth Alan, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Newman, Donald James, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Nykamp, Hugo John, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      1926-2012
    - Patterson, Robert Eric, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Phillips, Paul Joseph, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Port, Alan Jerome, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Robbin, James, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      1930-1983
    - Robinson, Warren Arthur, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Schryver, Herbert Francis, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Stewart, Edward William, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Stoll, Robert Stephen, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Sutherland, Ceylon M., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Vega, Ramon Antonio, Jr., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      From Panama
    - Wilkes, Jack E., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Willson, John Ellis, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Wiswall, Irwin William, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Wyatt, David Earl, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Aaronson, Jules, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      1931-
    - Alexander, John Randall, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Bandemer, Herbert Leo, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Beck, Donald George, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Braemer, Allen Charles, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Calnek, Bruce Wixson, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      1932-
      See also Faculty file and Collection #24-02-3346, Calnek, Bruce W. papers, 1947-2001
    - Childress, James Paul, Jr., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Clausen, Alfred Christian, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Cornell, Robert Eastwood, Jr., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Delgado, Richard James, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Dietrich, Herbert Chris, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Flemer, John Wilkinson, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Freeman, Max Eugene, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Friderici, Arthur Jonas, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Friedlander, Alfred Irwin, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 43)
      1930-1963
    - Galpin, Samuel Judson, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Garbutt, Thomas Wallace, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Greenberg, Myles Adrian, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Harling, David Evian, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Hershhorn, Bernard Seymour, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Hillman, Robert Bryant, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Hochman, Howard Allen, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Holmes, Frederick Milton, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Johnston, William Leon, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Kelley, Patrick Edward, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Kennedy, Robert Lawrence, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 54)
      1931-2013
    - Kohler, Robert Gordon, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 55)
      1931-1970
    - Kowalk, Arthur John, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Kradel, David Charles, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 57)
      1930-2006
    - Krohn, Frank Leo, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Leskovar, Richard Frank, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Little, Robert George, Jr., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Manning, Robert Victor, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 61)
      1924-2006
    - McBride, Douglas Frank, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Meek, John Clark, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Murtha, Thomas Joseph, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Pelloth, Donald Edward, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Pentek, John, Jr., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Presley, Edwin T., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Rasmusen, Benjamin Arthur, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Robens [Newman], Jane F., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Sacks, Gerald Jay, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Saunders, Burton, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Stuart, Joseph, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Terwilliger, Howard John, Jr., 1955 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      1931-1971
    - Tweddle, Harry VanDewater, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - VanName, Richard Charles, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Wallace, Lee Arthur, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      1925-2010
    - Barrett, Robert Bruce, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 77)
      1926-1987
    - Bartlett, Mendell Parker, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Brown, Bradford Bryant, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 79)
      1929-2011
    - Clark, Stillman Bailey, III, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 80)
      1929-2012
    - Dueland, Rudolf, Jr., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 81)
      1933-
    - Durland, Charles Evans, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Fallon, Edward Hagyard, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Fox, Donald Cummings, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Frey, Richard Francis, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Frumerie, Charles Morris, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Gillett, Roger Edward, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 87)
      1933-2009
    - Gilman, Michael Henry, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Grace, William John, Jr., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Graves, Rodney Stasch, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Hahn, George Edward, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 91)
      1932-2014
    - Haines, John Malcolm, V, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 92)
      1928-2002
    - Halestrap, Albert Joseph, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Halperin, Robert Samuel, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Hewes, Roland Porter, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Howe, John D., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Huyler, Peter Alvin, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Jeffrey, Graham Booth, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Kircher, Charles Austin, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Larrow, Larry Lloyd, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Layton, Gordon Eugene, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Mebus, Charles Albert, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Melberg, Willy Emil, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Moore, Earl Neil, Jr., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Newman, Louis Edward, III, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Newman, Martin Joseph, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Perona, Emil Enrione, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 107)
      1931-2009
    - Perper, Robert J., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 108)
      1933-2001
    - Pick, Norman, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 109)
      1926-2005
    - Reid, Charles Feder, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Rosenoff, Herbert Jay, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Sanford, Thomas Taylor, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 112)
      1932-2011
    - Schwirck, Stephen Halper, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Shumway, John David, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Simensen, Alfred Martin, Jr., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 115)
      1930-1995
    - Squire, Robert Alfred, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 116)
      1930-2011
    - Steinhoff, Alfred Charles, Jr., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Sumner, William Arthur, Jr., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Tanzer, Herbert, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Van Wyk, Teunis Willem, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Vrooman, Vernon Paul, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 121)
      1922-1961
    - Wagner, William Charles, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 122)
      1932-2012
    - Watson, Lewis Edwin, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - Wente, Robert Olliver, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Williams, Robert Vern, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 125)
      1926-2008
    - York, Robert Myron, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Zweighaft, Harold Murray, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - Abbott, Richard Jayne, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - Ahearne, Allan Joseph, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - Baker, William Herbert, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 130)
      1942-
    - Berman, Lewis Howard, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 131)
      1935-
    - Bezner, Gerald Arthur, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - Briggs, Robert Harold, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 133)